{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "Which attribute should have a tag in order to show a title tooltip as default?",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "It is not possible, you have to use JS",
                "Title attribute",
                "Tooltip attribute",
                "Name attribute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is difference between ul and ol?",
            "answer": "0",
            "options": [
                "OL element is a numbered list and UL is a list of points",
                "It is the same behavior",
                "None of these is a list",
                "UL element is a numbered list and ol is list of points "
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is block element?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "An Element that a specific size",
                "A divisor element",
                "A HTML element that occupies 100% of the hieght ot its container",
                "A HTML element that occupies 100% of the width ot its container"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Name three new tag from HTML5 that different from canvas?",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "div, img, ul",
                "Aside, figure, h1",
                "Article aside and nav",
                "Header, div, a"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is purpose of run method on Angular?",
            "answer": "0",
            "options": [
                "It is executed after the injector is created and are used to kickstart the application",
                "It's to extend the logic of each controller",
                "It's a method to load any data",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is scope?",
            "answer": "0",
            "options": [
                "A angular function to create methods",
                "A controller to be used in a component",
                "A build in object, which contains application data and methods",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Flexbox?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "A Tag HTML",
                "a HTML alignment",
                "A layout specification for css",
                "A HTML attribute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the purpose of translate property on CSS3?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "It is not a CSS property",
                "It is for translate texts",
                "It is to reposition an element in horizontal and veritical direction",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": " What mean of the a in RGBa?",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "alpha",
                "alpha color",
                "arrow",
                "any"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you set multiple box-shadows?",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do four values work on padding",
            "answer": "3",
            "options": [
                "top, bottom, left, right",
                "up, down, front, behind",
                "top, right, bottom, left",
                "left, right, right, left"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following property is used to underline color change.",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "text-decoration",
                "text-decoration-color",
                "text-decoration-style",
                "text-decoration-line"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Can we set the float center?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In CSS, what is the correct option to select only the heading with class name 'success'?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "#success { }",
                ".success { }",
                "success { }",
                ".class success {}"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Closure?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "Callback",
                "Module",
                "Function",
                "Service"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "typeof null",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "object",
                "undefined",
                "function",
                "string"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "'iPariksha is the practical Pariskha. Ipariksha is more Pariksha'.replace('Pariksha','test') output string will be",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "'itest is the practical test. Ipariksha is more test'",
                "'itest is the practical test. Itest is more test'",
                "'itest is the practical Pariskha. Ipariksha is more Pariksha'",
                "'iPariksha is the practical test. Ipariksha is more test'"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How can add a row using SQL in a database ?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "ADD",
                "CREATE",
                "INSERT",
                "MAKE"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The command to remove rows from a table 'QUESTIONS' is?",
            "answer": "2",
            "options": [
                "REMOVE FROM QUESTIONS",
                "DROP FROM QUESTIONS",
                "DELETE FROM QUESTIONS WHERE ..",
                "UPDATE FROM QUESTIONS"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The SQL WHERE clause:?",
            "answer": "1",
            "options": [
                "limits the column data that are returned",
                "limits the row data are returned.",
                "Both A and B are correct.",
                "Neither A nor B are correct."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the original purpose of SQL?",
            "answer": "3",
            "options": [
                "To specify the syntax and semantics of SQL data definition language",
                "To specify the syntax and semantics of SQL manipulation language",
                "To define the data structures",
                "All of above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "A view is which of the following?",
            "answer": "0",
            "options": [
                "A virtual table that can be accessed via SQL commands",
                "A virtual table that cannot be accessed via SQL commands",
                "A base table that can be accessed via SQL commands",
                "A base table that cannot be accessed via SQL commands"
            ]
        }
    ]
}